Welcome to Thursday, both the nickel and the
bank were seen moving differently for the
week, first of all, let me tell you about the outlook and
week, what is the sacrifice on the market for
good, good morning, morning ji, the market has
maintained quality for two-three days, but
as you know, from 3596 onwards, the market trend has
changed, caste or visual aids and noble
market surprising and observe whatever
half an hour of election and Corbett,
this GST of ours, no word to change for selves, no
two opinions sir, Diwali is
at 12000 and Bank Nifty is 26 thousand plus, sister
Shweta, I am still very
positive and do not look at the index because
today because of Reliance, it is a very cute
market, do not remain very strong, the
results, see if it has
outperformed a lot in the war, let me give you an update,
I
am free from date,
why is it election time and 12000 and 246
Jhalar Bank Nifty, on Diwali I had given you
BL, it hit 91  It was
2750 in PHC, it became gay, I remained in this game, a
lot of miss channel number set against that
person on multi lemon, apart from that on me,
I had told you very loudly that Godrej Properties and IT property will be done next
and I request you in
2021, just follow the real estate, so
Godrej Properties is editing new highs and
lows development, stay tuned, at this time I will
not give recommendation because my call was at the lower price,
now you went, I have two calls, both are
by, if you say, should I start, sir,
please tell me, friend, there is a change in telecom,
today's phone bill Aadhar number which you get,
Reliance Jio, is very good, but hey,
Indian and of this Idea
Idea numbers 90, which are theirs and Pooja,
there ice closed 240 386 Shubha is coming
in Idea, this price is Rajdhani and
now Vodafone
quote in this Idea has gone up, very good player, so
take today's stoploss at 7.50 in Idea Remind 66808  I
kept its
target of 12 but it was cheated inside me
and the other one is Gyan Bharti very very
reasonable and best performers on the art,
on the beginning market share of 28.29,
take shop launch of 438, target is 4520, so
these are two common telecom stocks
where I have the opinion to buy but
Abhishek Jain answer telecom stocks rise,
both of these have fallen down, wait to buy it,
I will not come, do it and if
it goes then the numbers of banks IndusInd Bank Bharti
Airtel will remain WhatsApp and as much as
one of our commissioners will be seen in the market,
if you are an advocate then subscribe to it in Amazing, it will
appoint you a little inside, so here it is a
little too far